{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":33,
 "infinite":false,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztm0sOwjAMRL3jQFyQc7GE62TXC6AiIlVWmx9pPI1n8Tao0InnpVVBBJFHIAScRdHzs1o4Y00jzomAXovVfEd0d5Z\/Le7kso3YE3vve3Xq+x9eg9d81t63cGtWruzlaOgkvUSm1ssbqQbFS+s5pChxM7XvST3WTm7dRCbnZspJ69kezdo6B3P1yZVyU79+B17PW0RWrHPs5PpineMquaJfq2v00l\/\/qLlKvAxCL2ftHzXXkZf6OHo5Z\/+oueil7\/5Rc9FL3\/2j5trzUh\/D5555+0fNRS9994+ai1767h81F7303T9qrpLnHno5b\/+ouf718g6whshTYZ2HudrQfrX8Donk5ZonXi+RruW\/XF+YK0+pl0Ho5Yz9o+ail777R81FL333j5qrxssg9HK2\/lFztXq5CKaX+j8i1nmYq42tl9rJ3HdFWzdRsZ5vxHoOVyXn5JGX8Z6OCoKb8Z5C6ihxMuUlMiheWs9hBo7ma52LXvolNd8R5+mVdeuEBy9r8iD51XN9Z82r9FzWnvVYTy9XrPKP2i\/WfRFSywfS6kKd",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":166,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztm0FugzAQRdnlQL5gz5UlV+oFWhZI1DWuP7ZnBvqe9DcJwd+TRyIUZVkA4vO5LB\/HjDzXlczYk8WaEcj34jXfmeeurTHCvyvu\/NXN4poovW4N4PZqvOdZ176HW0\/Nnb20Tm0P3t2eFrwc42dtvlteREoUL73nUJtP6brJ91Bzkuixt7CM9xxaUnOz5qTPRM+hl0b0XjU38bIfemlc8TLhpQy9NPZeSfgux0sdemmceZkfh5d90EsDL22glwZe2kAvjZKX+THc9\/RDLw28tIFeGnhpA7008NIGemm03PfgZT\/00uj1MgXa0\/u7yzHefXYC9\/qRKOR+XfkdMpKX8AxavdzAS7ACLyEieAkRUbzc2B9f8RImkjLH7u5l\/j8R7z479NJQvMyfW28Qn6n+xnsOd07rZ2XJzRQ0EdyMPJ+oaXVyo+Rl9ETx0nsOT8jZfL174eX\/TW2+FuuM6np0QnFoBhZeKn0i+TVyf7Pm1bpW7zk96X1\/vGdhfb3M2QXAPL4Aypgwmg==",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":166,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":712,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":48
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":713,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":688,
                 "y":40
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":714,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":735,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":758,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":759,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":761,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":765,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":64,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":768,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":772,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":368,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":774,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":784,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":976,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":672,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":789,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1256,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":794,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":384,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":795,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":797,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":798,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":208
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":800,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":801,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":802,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":755,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":756,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":757,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1248,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":770,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":793,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":816,
                 "y":16
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":799,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":512,
                 "y":256
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":803,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tiledversion":"1.1.6",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":198,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":235,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":259,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":287,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":450,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":821,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1126,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1321,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3305,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3531,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3819,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4051,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4115,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/breakable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4425,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5866,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5998,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6073,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6427,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6885,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6890,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6932,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7136,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7358,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7643,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "type":"map",
 "version":1,
 "width":166
}